Well, the president has numerous authorities to ensure public safety and order in our communities.
The president has the authority to send in the National Guard.
The president has the authority to surgeon federal law enforcement.
The president has the authority under 287G to deputize officials across the country to
engage in immigration and customs enforcement work and many other tools.
And, of course, the Insurrection Act is one lawful statutory tool at the president's disposal.
I think the most important point to convey tonight, Laura, is that the president is not
going to allow Americans, American citizens to be raped, murdered, maimed and killed
by illegal alien gangbangers, terrorists, drug dealers and psychopaths.
And we're not going to leave our citizens at the mercy of a Democrat criminal justice
system that frees serial repeat offenders to stab women in subways, to break into people's
homes and stab little children to death in their beds and to unleash this reign of terror
on our citizens.
President Trump is not going to stand for it.
That's the bottom line.
Stephen AOC is your your her favorite target, apparently on Instagram.
Check this out.
He looks like he is angry about the fact that he's 410 and he looks like he is so mad that
he is 410 that he's taken that anger out at any other population possible.
Like laugh at them.
Laugh at them.